Guide to the Crawford Theater Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Playbills and Programs, 1663-1989; Series I
  - Subseries B:, 1663-1860; Series I; 2.75 linear feet (11 boxes) Largest dimension: 17"
    - British Isles
      - England
        - London
          - Tottenham Street, 1830 (Box 27, Folder 208)
          - Vauxhall Royal Gardens, 1824, 1830-1841, 1853 (Box 27, Folder 209)
          - Victoria, 1834-1838, 1844, 1852-1857 (Box 27, Folder 210)
          - West London, 1822-1826 (Box 27, Folder 211)
          - Miscellaneous London theaters (C-S), 1728, 1759, 1785, 1809, 1831-1838, 1845-1851, 1858 (Box 27, Folder 212)
        - Manchester, 1792-1797, 1830, 1837, undated (Box 27, Folder 213)
        - Middlesex, 1847 (Box 27, Folder 214)
        - Scarborough, 1814, 1823 (Box 27, Folder 215)
        - Sheffield, 1817 (Box 27, Folder 216)
        - Stockton, 1824 (Box 27, Folder 217)
        - York, 1794, 1857 (Box 27, Folder 218)
        - Miscellaneous English cities (M-W), 1728, 1759, 1785, 1809, 1831-1838, 1845-1851, 1858 (Box 27, Folder 219)
      - Ireland
        - Dublin, 1808-1810, 1828-1852, undated (Box 27, Folder 220-221)
        - Ennis, 1755-1756 (Box 27, Folder 222)
        - Londonderry, 1795 (Box 27, Folder 223)
      - Scotland
        - Edinburgh, 1768-1780, 1808-1821, 1828-1829, 1834, 1842-1849 (Box 27, Folder 224-225)
        - Glasgow, 1808, 1815-1816, 1822 (Box 27, Folder 226)
    - Unidentified British Isles, 1789, 1817-1820, 1826 (Box 27, Folder 227)
    - United States
      - Baltimore
        - Baltimore Theatre, 1787, 1798, 1804 April-Nov, 1805 April-Nov, 1809, 1815, 1820-1823, 1828-1833 (Box 28, Folder 228-233)
        - Holliday Street, 1823, 1858-1860 (Box 28, Folder 234-235)
        - New Theatre, 1804-1805 January-April (Box 28, Folder 236-237)
        - Miscellaneous Baltimore theaters (A-F), 1833-1834, 1843, 1859 (Box 28, Folder 238)
      - Boston
        - Boston Museum, 1841-1859 (Box 29, Folder 239-240)
        - Boston Theatre, 1794-1795, 1806, 1811, 1818-1819, 1824, 1858 (Box 29, Folder 241)
        - Federal Street, 1819, 1824-1826 (Box 29, Folder 242)
        - Howard Athenaeum, 1848, 1858-1860 (Box 29, Folder 243)
        - National, 1837-1853 (Box 29, Folder 244)
        - Warren/Warren National, 1832-1836 (Box 29, Folder 245)
        - Miscellaneous Boston theaters (A-R), 1778, 1795, 1804, 1860 (Box 29, Folder 246)
      - Cincinnati
        - Cincinnati Theatre, 1832 (Box 29, Folder 247)
        - National Unidentified, 1843, n.d (Box 29, Folder 248)
      - Louisville, 1832 (Box 29, Folder 249)
      - Memphis, 1859 (Box 29, Folder 250)
      - Montgomery, 1835 (Box 29, Folder 251)
      - Nashville
        - New Theatre, 1827 (Box 29, Folder 252)
      - New Haven
        - Brewster Hall/Brewster's Hall, 1853, 1860, undated (Box 29, Folder 253)
        - Exchange Saloon, 1842 (Box 29, Folder 254)
        - Miscellaneous New Haven, theaters (M-Y), undated (Box 29, Folder 255)
      - New Orleans
        - American, 1828-1833 (Box 29, Folder 256)
        - Saint Charles, 1835, 1844-1845, undated (Box 29, Folder 257)
        - Spalding and Rogers' Amphitheatre, 1857-1858 (Box 29, Folder 258)
        - Miscellaneous New Orleans theaters (S), 1830 (Box 29, Folder 259)
      - New York
        - American, 1833-1835, undated (Box 29, Folder 260-261)
        - Bowery, 1828, 1839, 1845-1848, 1858, undated (Box 29, Folder 262)
        - Castle Garden, 1852-1854 (Box 29, Folder 263)
        - Niblo's Garden, 1853-1860 (Box 29, Folder 264)
        - Park, 1792, 1809-1815, 1846 (Box 30, Folder 265)
        - Wallack's, 1854-1858 (Box 30, Folder 266)
        - Miscellaneous New York theaters (A-R); unidentified, 1750-1753, 1787, 1792-1794, 1834, 1845-1849, 1853-1860 (Box 30, Folder 267)
      - Philadelphia
        - Arch Street, 1845-1849, 1853-1860 (Box 30, Folder 268)
        - Chestnut Street, 1828-1839, 1848-1849, 1854 (Box 30, Folder 269)
        - New, 1794, 1822-1825 (Box 30, Folder 270)
        - Philadelphia, 1824-1826 (Box 30, Folder 271)
        - Walnut Street, 1820, 1829-1831, 1849-1852, 1860 (Box 30, Folder 272)
        - Miscellaneous Philadelphia theaters (A-W); unidentified, 1778, 1813, 1821-1822, 1834, 1841-1844, 1852-1857, undated (Box 30, Folder 273)
      - Saint Louis, 1827, 1846 (Box 30, Folder 274)
      - Washington, DC, 1800, 1820, 1832 (Box 30, Folder 275)
      - Other U.S. cities (A-T), 1799, 1808, 1816, 1825, 1835-1837, 1846-1853 (Box 30, Folder 276)
      - Unidentified U.S., 1799, 1824, 1832, 1844-1846, 1855 (Box 30, Folder 277)
    - Other nations
      - Australia
        - Sydney, 1852 (Box 30, Folder 278)
      - Austria
        - Vienna, 1846 (Box 30, Folder 279)
      - Belgium
        - Brussels, 1838 (Box 30, Folder 280)
      - Canada
        - Montreal, 1855 (Box 30, Folder 281)
      - France
        - Paris, 1828, 1841, 1850 (Box 30, Folder 282)
      - Germany, 1688 (Box 30, Folder 283)
  - Subseries C:, 1861-1971; Series I; 6.75 linear feet (27 boxes) Largest dimension: between 13" and 17"
    The material within this subseries is arranged alphabetically in the following manner:
    British Isles: first by country, then by city, then by theater
    United States: first by state, then by city, then by theater
    Other Nations: first by country, then by city, then by theater
    Programs for theaters with similar names, or theaters whose names were changed slightly are filed in the same folder, e.g.:
    Her Majesty's/His Majesty's Tony Pastor's/Tony Pastor's Fourteenth Street/Tony Pastor's New
    Souvenir programs from U.S. tours of American and foreign dance companies follow the alphabetical run of U.S. programs in box 53.
    Material documenting performances in cities and theaters not listed may be found in the miscellaneous and unidentified files which follow the material for a particular country or city.
    - British Isles
      - England
        - Glyndebourne
          - Glyndebourne Festival Opera, 1957, 1964, 1967, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 284-287)
        - Liverpool, 1874, 1894-1903, undated (Box 31, Folder 288)
        - London
          - Alhambra/Alhambra Palace, 1869-1875 (Box 31, Folder 289)
          - Covent Garden, 1867, 1872, 1878-1879, 1885, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 290)
          - Drury Lane, 1864-1873, 1884-1886, 1898-1908 (Box 31, Folder 291-292)
          - Drury Lane, 1909, 1916-1918 (Box 32, Folder 293-294)
          - Her Majesty's, 1898-1899 (Box 32, Folder 295)
          - Her Majesty's/His Majesty's, 1900-1903 (Box 32, Folder 296)
          - His Majesty's, 1906 (Box 32, Folder 297)
          - Lyceum, 1876, 1899-1900 (Box 32, Folder 298)
          - Middle Temple Hall and Gardens, 1916, undated (Box 32, Folder 299)
          - Royal Strand/Strand, 1868-[1871?] (Box 32, Folder 300)
          - Miscellaneous London theaters (A-O), 1869-1870, 1878, 1886, 1901, 1934, 1958-1959, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 301)
          - Miscellaneous London theaters (P-R), 1898-1902, 1914, 1920-1921 (Box 33, Folder 302)
          - Miscellaneous London theaters (S-W), 1868-1870, 1884, 1891-1896 (Box 33, Folder 303)
          - Unidentified London, 1903-1905, undated (Box 33, Folder 304)
        - Stratford-upon-Avon, 1959-1961 (Box 33, Folder 305)
        - Miscellaneous English cities (B-P), 1862, 1877-1880, 1898, 1933, undated (Box 33, Folder 306)
        - Unidentified England, 1891, undated (Box 33, Folder 307)
      - Ireland
        - Dublin, 1876, 1881, undated (Box 33, Folder 308)
        - Wexford, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 309)
      - Scotland
        - Edinburgh, 1875-1876, 1898 (Box 33, Folder 310)
        - Glasgow, 1912 (Box 33, Folder 311)
      - Wales
        - Cardiff, 1898 (Box 33, Folder 312)
    - United States
      - Alabama
        - Mobile, 1868-1870 (Box 33, Folder 313)
      - Arkansas
        - Little Rock, 1885 (Box 33, Folder 314)
      - California
        - Los Angeles
          - Orpheum, 1896, 1904 (Box 33, Folder 315)
        - Pasadena
          - Pasadena Community Playhouse, 1932 (Box 33, Folder 316)
        - San Francisco
          - California/New California, 1870, 1879, 1891 (Box 33, Folder 317)
          - Miscellaneous California theaters (B-S), 1891-1897, undated (Box 33, Folder 318)
      - Colorado
        - Denver
          - Sixteenth Street, 1881 (Box 33, Folder 319)
        - Leadville
          - Globe, 1881 (Box 33, Folder 320)
      - Connecticut
        - Bridgeport, 1885, 1890, 1898 (Box 33, Folder 321)
        - Hartford
          - Jacobs and Proctor's Opera House/Proctor's Opera House, 1887-1893 (Box 33, Folder 322)
          - Parsons', 1903, undated (Box 33, Folder 323)
          - Miscellaneous Hartford theaters (A-P); unidentified, 1871-1875, 1885, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 324)
        - New Britain
          - Russwin Lyceum, 1893-1903 (Box 33, Folder 325)
        - New Haven
          - American/New American See also: box 36, folder 350, 1885 (Box 34, Folder 326)
          - Bunnell's Grand Opera House/ Bunnell's Museum/Bunnell's Grand Opera House and Museum, 1880, 1885-1888 March (Box 34, Folder 327)
          - Bunnell's Grand Opera House/Bunnell's Museum/Bunnell's Grand Opera House and Museum, 1888 April-1895, 1903-1904 (Box 34, Folder 328)
          - Carll's Opera House, 1881-1887 (Box 34, Folder 329)
          - Gaiety, 1879 (Box 35, Folder 330)
          - Hyperion, 1890-1894, 1895 March-1896 Jun, 1896 October-1897 Apr, 1897 October-1898, 1899-1902 May (Box 35, Folder 331-337)
          - Hyperion, 1902 October-1904 Apr, 1904 September-1907, 1912-1913, undated (Box 35, Folder 338-344)
          - Music Hall, 1868 (Box 35, Folder 345)
          - New Grand Opera House, 1895-1896 (Box 35, Folder 346)
          - Opera House, 1878-1883, 1889-1892 (Box 35, Folder 347)
          - Poli's/Poli's Wonderland, 1894, 1901-1903 (Box 36, Folder 348)
          - Shubert, 1916, 1927, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 349)
          - Theatre Comique See also: box 34, folder 326, 1887 (Box 36, Folder 350)
          - Yale School of Fine Arts/Yale University, 1904, 1916 (Box 36, Folder 351)
          - Miscellaneous New Haven theaters (A-P), 1881-1891, 1904, undated (Box 36, Folder 352)
          - Unidentified New Haven, 1877, undated (Box 36, Folder 353)
        - Wallingford
          - Oakdale Musical Theatre/Warwick Musical Theatre, undated (Box 36, Folder 354)
        - Miscellaneous Connecticut cities (A-M), 1871, 1878, 1886, 1898-1904, 1940, undated (Box 36, Folder 355)
        - Miscellaneous Connecticut cities (S-W), 1901-1903, 1931, undated (Box 36, Folder 356)
      - Florida
        - Fernandina, 1868 (Box 36, Folder 357)
      - Illinois
        - Chicago
          - Academy of Music/New Academy of Music, 1874, 1882 (Box 36, Folder 358)
          - Casino, 1888 (Box 36, Folder 359)
          - Grand Opera House, 1882-1885 (Box 36, Folder 360)
          - Haverly's, 1881-1884, undated (Box 36, Folder 361)
          - McVicker's, 1862, 1875, 1882-1886 (Box 36, Folder 362)
          - Park, 1888, undated (Box 36, Folder 363)
          - Miscellaneous Chicago theaters (C-V); unidentified, 1863-1864, 1869-1876, 1884-1885, 1894 (Box 36, Folder 364)
        - Peoria
          - Gable's Adelphi, 1884, undated (Box 36, Folder 365)
      - Indiana
        - Evansville
          - Apollo, 1880 (Box 36, Folder 366)
        - Indianapolis
          - Dickson's Grand Opera House/Dickson's New Grand Opera House/Grand Opera House, 1877-1882, 1889 (Box 36, Folder 367)
          - English's Opera House, 1880-1881 (Box 36, Folder 368)
          - Miscellaneous Indianapolis theaters (G-Z), 1881-1886, 1915 (Box 36, Folder 369)
      - Iowa, 1884, 1902-1903 (Box 36, Folder 370)
      - Kentucky
        - Louisville, 1869, 1872, 1881, undated (Box 36, Folder 371)
        - Miscellaneous Kentucky cities (C-L), 1883, 1936 (Box 36, Folder 372)
      - Louisiana
        - New Orleans
          - Farenta's Pavilion, undated (Box 37, Folder 373)
          - Miscellaneous New Orleans theaters (B-V); unidentified (Box 37, Folder 374)
      - Maine
        - Bangor
          - Bangor Opera House, 1887 (Box 37, Folder 375)
        - Portland
          - Jefferson, 1922-1926 (Box 37, Folder 376)
          - Miscellaneous Portland theaters (M-P); unidentified, 1883, 1891, 1897 (Box 37, Folder 377)
      - Maryland
        - Baltimore
          - Barton's Theatre-Comique, 1890 (Box 37, Folder 378)
          - Front Street Theatre Comique, 1871 (Box 37, Folder 379)
          - Holliday Street, 1861-1866, 1871 (Box 37, Folder 380)
          - Miscellaneous Baltimore theaters (F-K), 1886-1888, 1905 (Box 37, Folder 381)
      - Hagerstown
        - Academy of Music, 1896 (Box 37, Folder 382)
      - Massachusetts
        - Boston
          - Austin's Palace
            General note
            See: box 42, folder 434
          - Austin and Stone's/Austin and Stone's Museum/Austin and Stone's Boston Museum, 1884-1892 (Box 37, Folder 383)
            See also: box 43, folder 447
          - Bijou, 1883 (Box 37, Folder 384)
          - Boston Museum, 1861-1864, 1869-1879 June (Box 37, Folder 385-389)
          - Boston Museum, 1879 August-1890, undated (Box 38, Folder 390-398)
          - Boston Theatre, 1864-1885 (Box 39, Folder 399-406)
          - Boston Theatre, 1886-1893, undated (Box 40, Folder 407-408)
          - Boylston Museum, 1880-1881, 1885 (Box 40, Folder 409)
          - Colonial, 1913, 1920 (Box 40, Folder 410)
          - Forest Garden, 1880-1881 (Box 40, Folder 411)
          - Gaiety, 1878-1882 (Box 40, Folder 412-413)
          - Globe, 1871-1877, 1879 January-Jun, 1879 October-1880 May (Box 40, Folder 414-416)
          - Globe, 1880 June-1893 (Box 41, Folder 417-425)
          - Grand Opera House, 1888-1890, undated (Box 41, Folder 426)
          - Halleck's Alhambra, 1880-1881 (Box 41, Folder 427)
          - Hollis Street, 1886-1889, 1902 (Box 42, Folder 428-429)
          - Howard Athenaeum, 1861, 1867, 1872-1896, undated (Box 42, Folder 430-432)
          - Mechanics Building Auditorium, 1892-1896 (Box 42, Folder 433)
          - Palace/Austin's Palace, 1892-1896 (Box 42, Folder 434)
          - Park, 1879 April-1880 April (Box 42, Folder 435-437)
          - Park, 1880 May-1892 (Box 43, Folder 438-443)
          - Theatre Comique, 1865, undated (Box 43, Folder 444)
          - World's Museum, 1886-1888 (Box 43, Folder 445)
          - Miscellaneous Boston theaters (A-I), 1861, 1878-1882, 1888-1889, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 446)
          - Miscellaneous Boston theaters (L-W); unidentified, 1868-1869, 1879-1888, 1893-1894, undated (Box 43, Folder 447)
        - Lowell, 1885, 1892 (Box 43, Folder 448)
        - Lynn, 1880, 1886, 1893, undated (Box 43, Folder 449)
        - Miscellaneous Massachusetts cities, 1879-1890, 1923, 1939, undated (Box 43, Folder 450)
      - Michigan
        - Detroit
          - Opera House, 1880-1882 (Box 44, Folder 451)
          - Theatre Comique, 1873-1876 (Box 44, Folder 452)
          - Miscellaneous theaters (C-W); unidentified, 1884-1886, undated (Box 44, Folder 453)
        - Grand Rapids
          - Smith's Opera House, 1881, 1891, undated (Box 44, Folder 454)
      - Minnesota
        - Minneapolis
          - Grand Opera, 1884-1889 (Box 44, Folder 455-457)
          - Hennepin Avenue, 1887-1889 (Box 44, Folder 458)
          - Pence Opera House, undated (Box 44, Folder 459)
          - Miscellaneous Minneapolis theaters (B-L), 1890 (Box 44, Folder 460)
        - Saint Paul, 1885-1886, 1891 (Box 44, Folder 461)
      - Missouri
        - Kansas City
          - Coliseum, 1888 (Box 44, Folder 462)
        - Saint Louis
          - DeBar's Grand Opera House/DeBar's Opera House, 1872-1877 (Box 44, Folder 463)
          - Grand Opera House, 1879-1881 (Box 44, Folder 464)
            See also: box 44, folder 463
          - Olympic, 1868-1878, 1881 (Box 44, Folder 465)
          - Miscellaneous Saint Louis theaters (C-N); unidentified, 1881, 1888, undated (Box 44, Folder 466)
      - Nebraska
        - Lincoln
          - Funke's Opera House, 1890 (Box 44, Folder 467)
      - New Hampshire
        - Concord, undated (Box 44, Folder 468)
      - New Jersey
        - Atlantic City, 1886-1888, 1900, undated (Box 44, Folder 469)
        - Hoboken
          - Old Rialto, 1868, undated (Box 44, Folder 470)
          - Miscellaneous Hoboken theaters (A-H), 1902, undated (Box 44, Folder 471)
        - Jersey City
          - Bijou, 1900 (Box 44, Folder 472)
          - Theatre Comique, 1881, undated (Box 44, Folder 473)
          - Miscellaneous Jersey City theaters (G-N), 1878, 1893, 1898 (Box 44, Folder 474)
        - Miscellaneous New Jersey cities (B-W), 1885-1886, 1891-1893, 1903, 1939 (Box 44, Folder 475)
      - New York
        - Albany, 1871, 1884-1887, 1908 (Box 44, Folder 476)
        - Buffalo, 1881-1888, 1895, undated (Box 44, Folder 477)
        - New York City
          - Abbey's, 1893-1895 (Box 45, Folder 478)
          - Abbey's New Park, 1881-1882 (Box 45, Folder 479)
          - Academy of Music, 1875-1877, 1885-1886, 1892, undated (Box 45, Folder 480)
          - American/Aberle's American/Dick Parker's American (Third Avenue, between 30th and 31st), 1878-1880, n.d (Box 45, Folder 481)
          - American (Eighth Avenue, between 41st and 42nd), 1893-1895, 1904 (Box 45, Folder 482)
          - Bijou/Bijou Opera House, 1884-1888, 1896, 1903 (Box 45, Folder 483)
          - Booth's, 1869-1883 (Box 45, Folder 484-485)
          - Bowery/Fox's Bowery/Fox's Old Bowery, 1862-1865, 1874-1875 (Box 45, Folder 486)
          - Broadway, 1865, 1876-1879, 1888-1906, 1932, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 487-488)
          - Brooklyn Academy of Music, 1870-1897 (Box 45, Folder 489)
          - Brooklyn Grand Opera House, 1884-1890 (Box 45, Folder 490)
          - Brooklyn Park, 1870, 1878-1890 (Box 46, Folder 491)
          - Brooklyn Theatre/Mrs. F. B.Conway's Brooklyn Theatre, 1873-1876, 1884-1889 (Box 46, Folder 492)
          - Carnegie Hall, 1909, 1917, 1925-1931 (Box 46, Folder 493)
          - Casino, 1882-1888, 1890-1902, 1912, undated (Box 46, Folder 494-495)
          - Century, 1916-1917, 1924, 1928 (Box 46, Folder 496)
          - Criterion/Parker's Criterion, 1889, 1905, undated (Box 46, Folder 497)
          - Daly's/Daly's Fifth Avenue, 1870-1898 (Box 46, Folder 498-500)
          - Eagle, 1876-1877 (Box 46, Folder 501)
          - Fifth Avenue (Daly's), 1878-1890, 1899, 1911 (Box 47, Folder 502)
          - Fourteenth Street, 1881-1886, 1903, undated (Box 47, Folder 503)
          - Fox's Bowery/Fox's Old Bowery
            See: box 45, folder 486
          - Grand Opera House, 1869-1883, 1888-1901, 1913 (Box 47, Folder 504)
          - Hammerstein's Olympia/Hammerstein's Victoria, 1895-1902 (Box 47, Folder 505)
          - Harrigan's/Harrigan's Park, 1885-1893, undated (Box 47, Folder 506)
          - Haverly's, 1881-1884, undated (Box 47, Folder 507)
          - Henry C. (Harry) Miner's/H. C. Miner's American/Henry C.(Harry) Miner's Fifth Avenue/Henry C. (Harry) Miner's People's, 1878-1894, undated (Box 47, Folder 508)
            See also: box 49, folder 527
          - Hippodrome, 1913-1924, undated (Box 47, Folder 509-512)
          - Hyde and Behman's, 1880-1889 (Box 47, Folder 513)
          - Knickerbocker, 1911, 1925-1929, undated (Box 48, Folder 514-515)
          - Koster and Bial's Concert Hall/Koster and Bial's Music Hall, 1880, 1891-1899, undated (Box 48, Folder 516)
          - The Lambs', 1874, 1907, 1915 (Box 48, Folder 517)
          - Lina Edwin's, 1871-1872, undated (Box 48, Folder 518)
          - London, 1878-1883, 1892, 1897, undated (Box 48, Folder 519)
          - Lyceum, 1875-1878, 1882-1885, undated (Box 48, Folder 520)
          - Lyric, 1908, 1914, 1928 (Box 48, Folder 521)
          - Madison Square Garden/Madison Square Theatre/Garden Theatre, 1883, 1890-1894, 1944, undated (Box 48, Folder 522)
          - Manhattan Opera House, 1925-1926 (Box 48, Folder 523)
          - Metropolitan Opera House, 1886-1902, 1907 (Box 48, Folder 524)
          - Metropolitan Opera House, 1918, 1924, 1937, 1949, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 525-526)
          - Miner's Eighth Avenue, 1908, undated (Box 49, Folder 527)
          - National Garden Variety/New National, 1876-1881 (Box 49, Folder 528)
          - New Amsterdam, 1916, 1927 (Box 49, Folder 529)
          - New Park (Brooklyn), 1874-1876, 1884 (Box 49, Folder 530)
          - Niblo's Garden, 1870-1887, 1894-1895, undated (Box 49, Folder 531-532)
          - Olympic, 1863-1864, 1871-1877 (Box 49, Folder 533)
          - Olympic (Brooklyn), 1873-1874, 1880, 1897 (Box 49, Folder 534)
          - Parepa Hall, 1878-1879, undated (Box 49, Folder 535)
          - Park, 1874-1878, 1884-1885 (Box 49, Folder 536)
          - Proctor's/Proctor's Ladies' Club/Proctor's Novelty, 1887, 1894-1898 (Box 49, Folder 537)
          - Standard, 1878-1880 (Box 49, Folder 538)
          - Star, 1883-1894, 1899 (Box 49, Folder 539)
          - Theatre Comique, 1867-1868, 1875-1884, undated (Box 49, Folder 540)
          - Tony Pastor's/Tony Pastor's Fourteenth Street/Tony Pastor's New, 1877-1880, 1887, 1892, 1897-1900, undated (Box 49, Folder 541)
          - Union Square, 1874-1877 (Box 49, Folder 542)
          - Union Square, 1878-1888 (Box 50, Folder 543)
          - Volks' Garden/Volksgarden, 1876-1879, undated (Box 50, Folder 544)
          - Volks Theatre (Brooklyn), 1880-1882 (Box 50, Folder 545)
          - Wallack's, 1866-1881 (Box 50, Folder 546-548)
          - Walter Hampden, 1928 (Box 50, Folder 549)
          - West Brighton Beach Hotel, 1883, undated (Box 50, Folder 550)
          - Winter Garden, 1864-1867 (Box 50, Folder 551)
          - Ziegfield, 1927-1928 (Box 50, Folder 552-553)
          - Miscellaneous New York City theaters (A-B), 1867-1880, 1890-1898, 1933, 1938, undated (Box 50, Folder 554)
          - Miscellaneous New York City theaters (C), 1864, 1874-1878, 1900, 1914-1915, 1936, 1963, undated (Box 50, Folder 555)
          - Miscellaneous New York City theaters (E-F), 1867, 1891, 1905, 1912, 1922 (Box 50, Folder 556)
          - Miscellaneous New York City theaters (G), 1874-1880, 1889, 1895-1899, 1905 (Box 50, Folder 557)
          - Miscellaneous New York City theaters (H-K), 1872, 1878-1881, 1887, 1896-1898, 1906, 1914, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 558)
          - Miscellaneous New York City theaters (L-M), 1863, 1880-1885, 1902-1903, 1918, 1925, 1937-1939, 1963, undated (Box 51, Folder 559)
          - Miscellaneous New York City theaters (N-P), 1862, 1877-1891, 1902, 1916, 1930, undated (Box 51, Folder 560)
          - Miscellaneous New York City theaters (R-T), 1875-1878, 1883-1884, 1891, 1898, 1910-1915, 1931, 1941, 1948, undated (Box 51, Folder 561)
          - Miscellaneous New York City theaters (V-Z), 1869-1872, 1878, 1891, 1913, undated (Box 51, Folder 562)
          - Unidentified New York City, 1885, 1910, undated (Box 51, Folder 563)
        - Oswego
          - Academy of Music, 1878, undated (Box 51, Folder 564)
        - Rochester
          - Academy of Music/Corinthian Academy of Music, 1880-1881 (Box 51, Folder 565)
          - Grand Opera House/Opera House, 1878-1884 (Box 51, Folder 566)
          - Miscellaneous Rochester theaters (H-L); unidentified, 1889, undated (Box 51, Folder 567)
        - Syracuse
          - Grand Opera House, 1881-1882 (Box 51, Folder 568)
          - Miscellaneous Syracuse theaters (W); unidentified, 1882, undated (Box 51, Folder 569)
        - Troy
          - Grand Central, 1884-1887 (Box 51, Folder 570)
          - National, 1886, undated (Box 51, Folder 571)
        - Miscellaneous cities, New York State (A-Y); unidentified, 1875-1889, 1911, 1937, undated (Box 51, Folder 572)
      - North Carolina
        - Chapel Hill
          - Playmakers, 1963-1967 (Box 52, Folder 573)
          - Roanoke Island, 1937-1938 (Box 52, Folder 574)